[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These are typical Australian animals except one.", "correct_answer": "Sloth", "incorrect_answers": ["Platypus", "Dingo", "Echidna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the classic movie The Sound of Music?", "correct_answer": "Robert Wise", "incorrect_answers": ["Fred Zinnemann", "Billy Wilder", "Frank Capra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does HAND mean in instant messaging language?", "correct_answer": "have a nice day", "incorrect_answers": ["hot always, never dull", "handsome and nearly divine", "had a neat dream"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does ludology study?", "correct_answer": "video games", "incorrect_answers": ["postcards", "wine", "the moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1965 this American singer and actress won her first Tony for her work on Flora the Red Menace. Her Oscar came in 1972 for Cabaret.", "correct_answer": "Liza Minelli", "incorrect_answers": ["Judy Garland", "Rita Moreno", "Madelyn Kahn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "History records the fact that a Roman senator named Nonius chose exile rather than surrender his precious stone to Mark Anthony. This is Nonius gem stone.", "correct_answer": "Opal", "incorrect_answers": ["Ruby", "Tourmaline", "Zircon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the name of the Aye-aye originate from according to common hypothesis?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["From the Malagasy expression for I dont know", "From the sound made by the animal", "From an exclamation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie won the 2005 Oscar for Best Documentary Feature?", "correct_answer": "The March of the Penguins", "incorrect_answers": ["Darwins Nightmare", "Murderball", "Street Fight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chinese people believe that 13 is a lucky number.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first nation to field a battle tank?", "correct_answer": "Britain", "incorrect_answers": ["The USA", "Germany", "Austria-Hungary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "American artist and filmmaker Andy Warhol, a major figure in the Pop Art movement, is of Slovakian origin.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Grammys did Tina Turner win in 1985 for the song Whats Love Got To Do With It?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "4", "1"]}]